Finding Aid for Integrated Premedical-Medical Program (University of Michigan) records, 1972-2002
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Student Life 1972-2000
  - Awards
    - Colton Scholarship 1994-1999 (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous Awards and Letters 1986-1998 (Box 6)
    - Phi Beta Kappa 1982-1997
      [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2072 ]
    - Frank E. Robbins Award 1984-1998, 6 folders (Box 6)
    - Shipman Scholarship 1995-1999 (Box 6)
    - Dr. Jane Skillen Memorial Award 1988-1999 (Box 6)
  - Class Lists 1978-2003 (Box 6)
  - Commencement Brunch 1989-1992 (Box 6)
  - Convocation 1988-1998 (Box 6)
  - Director Announcements 1998 (Box 6)
  - Disabled Students 1984 (Box 6)
  - Housing 1972-1986 (Box 6)
  - Orientation 1982-1997 (Box 6)
  - Student Representatives
    - Committee Rosters 1977-1999 (Box 6)
    - Community Service
      - General Activities 1997-1998 (Box 6)
      - Charity Week
        - 1988-1996 (Box 6)
        - 1997 (Box 6)
        - 1998 (Box 6)
        - 1999 (Box 6)
        - I-Ball Tickets and Invitations 1988-2000 (Box 6)
    - Inteflex Student Council Agendas and Minutes
      - Constitution 1991 (Box 6)
      - 1977-1988 (Box 6)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 6)
      - 1992-1996 (Box 6)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 6)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 6)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 6)
      - 1999 (Box 6)
  - Tutoring 1978-1993 (Box 6)
  - Weekly Announcements 1997-1999 (Box 6)
- Visual Materials 1973-2000
  The Visual Materials series, 1973-2002 (1.1 linear feet) contains scrapbook materials, photographs, and videotapes. One Inteflex scrapbook was created by Inteflex office staff. The rest of the clippings are loose materials collected with the intention of creating another scrapbook. Photographs are separated into faculty and staff, student life, and photograph albums. While there are few images of the administration, there are many photographs of students. There are formal and informal collages of class members under class photos. Snapshots of student activities are filed under yearly activities. There are also two photograph albums, one showing student life and the other containing images from students' internships (or preceptorships) with Michigan doctors. There are also three VHS videotapes in the records. Two videotapes are of special events: The annual charity I-Ball from 1997, and the 1998 Convocation. The third was created by students during the 1998 charity week. It follows students through dorms and classroom buildings for "Jail & Bail" activities and also documents a charity auction aimed at Inteflex students.
  - Photographs
    - Faculty and Staff
      - General undated (Box 6)
      - Picnic 1987 (Box 6)
      - Robert Johnson's Retirement 1987 (Box 6)
    - Student Life
      - General undated (Box 6)
      - Class Photos
        - 1978-1979 (Box 6)
          (photocopies only, copy negative for 1979)
        - 1980-1982, roll negatives (Box 6)
        - [1983] Entering Class of 1977-[1986/1987] Entering Class of 1980 (copy negatives) (Box 6)
        - [1987/1988] Entering Class of 1981-[1990] Entering Class of 1983 (Box 6)
          (see also oversized folder UBImul C26)
        - 1991-1994 (Box 6)
        - 1995-1996 (Box 6)
        - 1997-1999 (Box 6)
        - 2000-2003 (Box 6)
          (copy negative for 2000 and 2003)
        - 2004-2006 (Box 6)
      - Yearly Activities
        - 1978 (Box 7)
        - 1979 (Box 7)
        - 1980
          - General (Box 7)
          - Alumni Reunion (Box 7)
        - 1981 (Box 7)
        - 1982 (Box 7)
        - 1983
          - General (Box 7)
          - Alumni Reunion (Box 7)
        - 1985 (Box 7)
        - 1986 (Box 7)
        - 1987
          - General (Box 7)
          - Graduation (Box 7)
          - I-Ball (Box 7)
        - 1988 (Box 7)
        - 1989
          - General (Box 7)
          - Picnic (Box 7)
          - Preceptorships (Box 7)
        - 1990 (Box 7)
        - 1991 (Box 7)
        - 1992 (Box 7)
        - 1993 (Box 7)
        - 1994
          - General (includes slides) (Box 7)
          - Inteflex Planning Meeting (Box 7)
        - 1995
          - General (includes slides) (Box 7)
          - I-Ball (Box 7)
          - Picnic (Box 7)
        - 1996 (includes slides) (Box 7)
        - 1997
          - General (includes slides) (Box 7)
          - Graduation Luncheon (Box 7)
          - Pie-in-the-Face Challenge (Box 7)
        - 1998 (Box 7)
  - Photograph Albums
    - Inteflex Activities 1984-1986 (Box 7)
    - Preceptor Photo Book 1983-1989 (Box 7)
  - Scrapbook Items
    - Inteflex Scrapbook 1981-1987 (Box 7)
    - Loose Clippings 1973-1996 (Box 7)
  - Video Tapes
    - Charity Week Activities (Auction, Jail & Bail) January 1998, VHS (Box 7)
    - I-Ball "Vision" (includes faculty and student speakers, guest speech by Dr. Ryler, and a student skit) 1997, VHS (Box 7)
    - Inteflex Convocation September 3, 1998, VHS (Box 7)
  - Roll Negatives (Box 7)